<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Auditing &#8211; Applicature</title>
	<atom:link href="https://applicature.com/product-category/auditing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://applicature.com</link>
	<description>Blockchain / Smart Contracts / Decentralized Apps</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 21:20:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://applicature.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/favicon2-100x100.png</url>
	<title>Auditing &#8211; Applicature</title>
	<link>https://applicature.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Your IEO Roadmap</title>
		<link>https://applicature.com/shop/auditing/your-ieo-roadmap</link>
					<comments>https://applicature.com/shop/auditing/your-ieo-roadmap#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nazar.khrupalo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 16:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://applicature.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=3903</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Discover a detailed way to get your project through IEO with our recommendations. Starting with project wrap-up till successful IEO!</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2><b>Why Your Blockchain Initiative Shouldn’t Miss Out on the Action in 2020?</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Initial Exchange Offering (IEO) has opened up new ways to raise funds in the blockchain community. Its main advantage is that the company founders don&#8217;t have to be token sale experts. </span></p>
<p><b>Benefits you get: </b></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">No need to deploy token sale cabinets.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">It is not mandatory to write complicated crowd-sale smart contracts for IEO.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Project promotion to exchange community.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exchange takes care of the entire campaign-launching process.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exchange verifies the AML/KYC compliance.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exchange takes care of the entire campaign-launching process.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><b>However there is a certain list of criteria you would need to follow:</b></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Written and audited Token Smart Contract is “must have” for IEO;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You will have to pass risk audit conducted by exchange: </span>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">set of partnerships and appropriate level of credibility of the project team would be validated manually;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You need to tell a super strong story of your project success;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You cannot start IEO processes without legal opinion.</span></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before being recommended to exchanges for IEO you would be willing to know the answers to the following questions: </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Can I even do an IEO?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">If I can do it, am I ready for an IEO?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Which exchange do I use?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">What can stop me here?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">What would be the expenses?</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It is hard to get exchanges, as they get hundreds of listing requests daily. Hence, you would need to be patient while preparing and finding a perfect match in terms of an exchange to use.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">What we can tell is that the first acquisitions on this super early, emerging market of blockchain technology are happening:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Binance, Bittrex, IDAX, LBank, CoinBene, Coineal, Digifinex, HitBtc have already launched their launchpads for IEO;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">20+ IEOs are published on ICObench today;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over 50 IEOs have already happened!</span></li>
</ul>
<p><b><i>“IEO is a very time sensitive and emerging crypto market niche to penetrate. You’ll want to make it happen in one shot, thus make sure you are ready for it 100%”</i></b></p>
<h2><b>We spotted IEO early on</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We have always been here looking into all possible options and ways to simplify project early-stage lifecycle!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">What has been noted in the scope of our market research and development since November 2018:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><b>The IEO topic raised in Korea in Autumn 2018, </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">and started getting popular among Korean Exchanges;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Binance restarted IEO in February 2019 with the success of BitTorrent, from where this type of fundraising started to get popular;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the last two months market got a slight understanding of what IEO is and what is needed to be successful there. There are still multiple questions based on lack of understanding of the process;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Based on the example of RAID project that lost its partnership with OP.GG several days before planned IEO on Bittrex, and eventually lost their right to run this IEO due to project credibility, we can say: </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;Today, Major Exchanges can provide a proper and in-depth analysis of a project. Potential Token buyers can get more explicit information about the reliability of a Startup, and reactions to malicious activities of the project team are easier to spot&#8221;.</span></i></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The scope of the &#8220;must-have&#8221; project parts had significantly expanded since the days of hyped ICO market. The major metrics of project credibility today are:</span>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">B2B relations</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">reliable partnerships</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">technology determination;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">detailed projects roadmap proving the potential to grow;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">strong story to tell;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">detailed and forward-looking projections of financial profitability;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">And, of course, traction on social media channels among early adopters &amp; investment community;</span></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2><b>We analyzed Market trends and Tokenization Options for you</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We have analyzed more than 2,000 concepts and researched more than 200 scenarios over the past 12 months.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It’s our</span><b> full-time job</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to track innovators who are building blockchain products and key decision-makers in the enterprise world who are hunting for best use cases and avenues for blockchain adoption, as well as the technology to acquire further down the path.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since January 2019, we have picked up our connections with Major Exchanges and gathered all required set of infographics to bring our projects to the table of IEO discussion.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To be honest with you, we discuss crowdfunding campaigns with our clients every day. We have been with projects since 2017, and have guided project teams in the bearish market of autumn 2018 and beginning of 2019. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Everything is telling us that after all we&#8217;ve seen &#8211; 2019 is the time to look for new ways of crowdfunding:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You will have competition that doesn’t sleep. Even though it’s early on, we have seen equally good teams starting similar products, and some of them have raised seed funding and Series A. The space will inevitably become more crowded.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">2019 is the year of first significant acquisitions. It’s already starting slowly, but as the first movers are making their bets, competitors will follow shopping for similar solutions only because that’s how markets work: large players follow each other in their strategic moves.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We are getting closer and closer to the point of mass adoption. It is yet too early to say that it is happening today, however we assume that by year 2030 distributed technologies and crypto currencies will be as common as 3G internet on your mobile phone in 2019.</span></li>
</ul>
<h2><b>What exactly is IEO Review and Recommendations?</b></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We will get into the initial high-level review and validation for IEO</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">After the validation, we will introduce you to the </span><b>Legal Advisor </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">to find out the right path to IEO, and if this path is even available</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A dedicated team of Business Analysts will review your materials for IEO in detail</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We will set up an auditing campaign to get a deep understanding of your current situation, features, maturity, advantages, and potential vulnerabilities</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">To make your project more investment-ready, we will provide you with a set of recommendations for upgrades</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We will emphasize points of attraction and will raise red flags for bottlenecks and pit-holes of the projects </span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Deliverables:</span></p>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Internal Project Review Document.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">360 Recommendations List.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We may forward your project for exchange review in case if it is ready for IEO according to our assessment.</span></li>
</ol>
<p><b>Bonus:</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Set of use cases applicable for your startup enhancement </span></p>
<h2><b>What Will Happen the Next Business Day After You Order?</b></h2>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We will schedule a call with you to dive deep into your situation. The duration of the call could be as long as 2 hours if we need to focus on certain areas of potential explosion. If you cannot dedicate 2 hours in a one-time slot, we will schedule a follow-up call.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">After we have the call, we will set a timeline for preparation of an individualized blueprint for you (usually takes between 5 days and 3 weeks).</span></li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://applicature.com/shop/auditing/your-ieo-roadmap/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smart Contract Expert Review</title>
		<link>https://applicature.com/shop/auditing/expert-recommendations-and-report-for-your-smart-contract</link>
					<comments>https://applicature.com/shop/auditing/expert-recommendations-and-report-for-your-smart-contract#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nazar.khrupalo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 10:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://applicature.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=3816</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Get your Smart Contracts Validated and solidified in a session with our experts, followed up with an explicit Recommendations for your future reference.</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2><b>Why Your Blockchain Initiative Won’t Miss Out on the Action in 2019</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">2019 has started exactly as we predicted…</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">First acquisitions on the super early, emerging market of blockchain technology are happening:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Facebook has announced the acquisition of ChainSpace</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bakkt, backed by the New York Stock Exchange, has proceeded with its first acquisition in Starbucks</span></li>
</ul>
<h2><b>We Knew Smart-Contract Technology Was Here to Stay</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Blockchain is now disrupting and penetrating all business verticals!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Around </span><b>100 Smart Contracts for the Ethereum Network are being deployed and validated on Etherscan daily</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">. At the moment of this writing, there are over 1,200,000 smart contracts deployed on Ethereum, holding a total of over 100,000,000 ETH. Out of these contracts, over 50,000 have been verified on Etherscan. This is a 100-fold increase in the total number of Ethereum smart contracts in existence in just 2 years.</span></p>
<p><b>Well-known cases of loss of funds  during an ICO, including the Quadriga case and the numerous vulnerabilities found in smart contracts in the process of Constantinople hard fork, </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">are giving a clear signal: </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hackers still have room for action, that depends  on the </span></i><b><i>version of technology </i></b><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">used for development, </span></i><b><i>coding standards </i></b><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">to be followed, common </span></i><b><i>spelling errors</i></b><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and </span></i><b><i>lack of experience.</i></b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Are you ready to launch?</span></p>
<h2><b>We Have Worked Hard to Become Your Expert Guides</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We have analyzed more than 1,000 tokenization events, developed over 500 smart contracts, and researched more than 50 ERC standards in the last 12 months.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Through our relations with EEA and the Linux Foundation, we have access to early industry news and the latest technology updates, in line with our constant practices and implementations.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It’s our</span><b> full-time job</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to track innovators who are building blockchain products, and key decision-makers in the enterprise world who are hunting for the best implementation of their use cases and avenues in the form of smart-contract technology for acquisition further down the path.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you’re reading the news about another 51% attack or exchange has been hacked, you are probably asking yourself whether</span><b> YOUR SMART CONTRACT IS SECURE ENOUGH. OR CAN IT BE HACKED?</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Let’s be honest. We receive a lot of b.s. inquiries. All the token-sale hype has driven crowds of people into the industry and given them a good excuse to call themselves blockchain-based companies. We have also seen really good teams, projects, and companies evolve over the months and years.</span></p>
<h3><b>How to Build without Losing</b></h3>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Every smart contact you publish could potentially be a point of error for your business. Order NOW to get Expert Recommendations for improvements and standardized review by </span></i><b><i>Technology Leaders from the Market!</i></b></p>
<h2><b>What Exactly Is Included in Our Expert Recommendation and Report?</b></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A checklist with results of your smart-contract Review</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A high-level analysis of potential vulnerabilities and mistakes </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Recommendations on possible improvements that could be implemented and estimates of work required to improve your code</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Executive summary &#8211; a public document that you will be able to share with your community and investors in order to boost your credibility</span></li>
</ul>
<p><b>Bonus: </b><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">an honest insider review of the most frequently identified vulnerabilities based on our experience.</span></i></p>
<h2><b>What Will Happen the Next Business Day After You Order?</b></h2>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We will schedule a call with you to dive deep into your situation. The duration of the call could be as long as 2 hours if we need to focus on certain areas of potential explosion. If you cannot dedicate 2 hours in a one-time slot, we will schedule a follow-up call.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">After the call, we will set a timeline for preparation of an individualized blueprint for you (this usually takes between 2 days and 1.5 weeks).</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><b>Why It’s Risk-Free</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We have a 100% return policy on this product. If for any reason our work doesn’t turn out to be a good fit for you, we will refund your payment for this product, no questions asked. We do this because we are confident we can help you progress. We value successful partnerships more than anything else.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://applicature.com/shop/auditing/expert-recommendations-and-report-for-your-smart-contract/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
