<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Consulting &#8211; Applicature</title>
	<atom:link href="https://applicature.com/product-category/consulting/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://applicature.com</link>
	<description>Blockchain / Smart Contracts / Decentralized Apps</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 21:20:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://applicature.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/favicon2-100x100.png</url>
	<title>Consulting &#8211; Applicature</title>
	<link>https://applicature.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Your Blockchain Adoption Advisory</title>
		<link>https://applicature.com/shop/consulting/your-blockchain-adoption-advisory</link>
					<comments>https://applicature.com/shop/consulting/your-blockchain-adoption-advisory#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 08:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://applicature.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=6979</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Choosing the path to fundraising If you run a company or startup at the early stages of development looking for a way of raising some funds then this offer is a good match for you.  Currently, there are several options including IEO, STO, and ICO in the crypto environment. Each option goes with its pros [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Choosing the path to fundraising</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you run a company or startup at the early stages of development looking for a way of raising some funds then this offer is a good match for you. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Currently, there are several options including IEO, STO, and ICO in the crypto environment. Each option goes with its pros and cons. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Initial exchange offering is one of the most popular crowdfunding models as of today, as it provides a good level of security and is pretty simple within the process of launch. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Security token offering is the best way to sell security tokens being backed with the real-world value represented in stocks, bonds, and shares allowing the dividend distribution to investors. </span></p>
<p><b>How can we help you?</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our team of business analysts will analyze your project documentation and business model components in order to define the best-matching solution applicable to your exact situation. During the discovery session, we’ll elicit your current needs, problems, and intentions to find the appropriate solution for running the crowdfunding campaign.</span></p>
<p><b>What will you get?</b></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discovery session call</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Q&amp;A call with our recommendations </span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Document containing:</span></li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">the description of possible solutions </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">relative pros and cons</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">definition of the must-have actions or documents for each possible option</span></li>
</ul>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Blockchain Platform for Your Business</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Blockchain implementation has become a widespread means of technological advancement. Blockchain appears to be an integral part of the modern business strategy, as it solves a range of common issues. Since you’ve decided to run your business on top of blockchain, you’ve probably come to the point when you have to choose the best matching platform. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There exists a wide range of blockchains to choose from. To provide various options to cryptocurrency users as well as multi-purpose solutions and higher performance, a number of blockchain platforms have appeared, such as</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Ethereum, Litecoin, Hyperledger, Graphene, IOTA, Stellar, </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">and many others. All of these blockchains have a different approach to aspects of security, scalability, and performance. They also function on various consensus algorithms, providing support and functionality to various industry verticals.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus, in order to choose the right one, requirements regarding speed, scalability, security, and cost-efficiency should be taken into consideration.</span></p>
<p><b>How can we help you?</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We’ll be happy to jump on a discovery call to find out your current situation and see whether there is a need for blockchain implementation. Along with that, we’ll discuss your platform’s needs and expectations to choose the most applicable option for you.</span></p>
<p><b>What will you get?</b></p>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discovery session call</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Q&amp;A call with our recommendations</span></li>
<li>Document containing:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our recommendations regarding blockchain implementation</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A list of blockchain platforms that would solve the platform’s needs</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pros and cons overview of the proposed solution</span></li>
</ul>
<h2><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">Disclaimer</span></em></h2>
<p><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">* The offer is only applicable for projects that plan to launch their products or raising campaigns in 2020. We will award $1,000 only for those who have intentions of building further cooperation with us. Therefore, if you have any questions </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">please contact us before getting the coupon.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://applicature.com/shop/consulting/your-blockchain-adoption-advisory/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Startup Acceleration Advisory</title>
		<link>https://applicature.com/shop/consulting/startup-acceleration-advisory</link>
					<comments>https://applicature.com/shop/consulting/startup-acceleration-advisory#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 23:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://applicature.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=6933</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Disclaimer: This service is only available to a limited amount of companies within a limited list of categories, such as fintech, insurtech, healthtech, as well as those utilizing technologies of blockchain and AI. You are good if you received an invite from me for this service. If you have stumbled upon this page accidentally, please talk [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Disclaimer:</h3>
<p>This service is only available to a limited amount of companies<span style="font-weight: 400;"> within a limited list of categories, such as fintech, insurtech, healthtech, as well as those utilizing technologies of blockchain and AI</span>.</p>
<p>You are good if you received an invite from me for this service. If you have stumbled upon this page accidentally, please talk to us before purchasing the service as you will most probably just be refunded otherwise.</p>
<h3>Hello 😉</h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I&#8217;m Ian Arden, a serial entrepreneur,</span> technology advisor and recently a founder of a VC/LP focused project called <a href="https://milestonebased.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">milestoneBased</a>.</p>
<p>Due to the character of the business, I&#8217;m tightly engaged in the venture capital community.</p>
<h3>Advisory Format</h3>
<ol>
<li>Monthly advisory sessions</li>
<li>Email conversations</li>
<li>access to relevant materials, both pre-existing and compiled ad hoc for you by me and my team members <span style="font-weight: 400;">from investor outreach, consulting, and business development departments</span>.</li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">About Me</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Being naturally quite people-oriented, I’ve started my professional path as a software engineer back in University. I got to work on mission-critical projects that many others fell the victims of, such as a software package servicing the devices on the gas station, or an email database recovery tool that was later sold to one of the largest personal computer equipment manufacturers back in the 2000s.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Through one of my other companies focusing on accelerating technology businesses, we were able to help dozens of startup founders launch their products, get their first raise, get into accelerators and achieve leadership in their niches.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I’ve rebranded Applicature in 2017 and we managed to become one of the best-rated blockchain innovation companies, with dozens of proofs of concept and MVPs done, as well as multiple token sale projects.</span></p>
<h3>Why I am doing this</h3>
<p>I have accumulated a lot of resources I’m happy to share with you.</p>
<p>It’s worth noting I’m providing this advisory service due to my involvement in milestoneBased &#8211; our new product destined to drastically increase the success rate for startups and drive capital raising costs and organizational overheads to zero.</p>
<p>(When our ultimate vision is implemented, entrepreneurs will have much easier access to capital, for less equity. In return, they’ll need to give something back: access to their ongoing traction data which will help build their unique entrepreneurial score.)</p>
<p>As such, my advisory for you is helping me improve and formalize my method, which I plan to put in the base of milestoneBased AI algorithm for startups roadmapping.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Roadmapping</h3>
<p>Roadmapping is a key method throughout the advisory engagement.</p>
<p>We design a roadmap in the form of a graph of milestones letting you get from where you are to where you want to get.</p>
<p>With milestones being highly structured and typed instances, one can simply tell whether a company is moving with the right speed and in the right direction by easily benchmarking against industry average indicators: from the number of deals in the pipeline to the count of code lines in your software produced monthly.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Through roadmapping, we also spot high-level inconsistencies, obstacles or missing pieces in your grand entrepreneurial plan, building a more definite path to your success.</p>
<p>Our advisory is organized in a form of 12 monthly sessions per year, between 1 and 2 hours each, with the email conversations between the session.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The goal of a session is to establish the roadmap and the interim goals for the next three months, as well as accountability of the previous month.</p>
<p>Not only this advisory is cost-efficient and packed with value, but it’s also a great way to establish accountability for your commitments and is a great driver for your further acceleration!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Resources Available</h3>
<p>While our time on the calls is limited, I’ll be sending multiple documents, templates, checklists and reading resources in these topics:</p>
<ol>
<li>Fund Raising
<ul>
<li>Lists of relevant investors &#8211; usually tailor-made</li>
<li>Messages and sequences</li>
<li>Pipeline management tips</li>
<li>Automation tips</li>
<li>Pitch deck feedback</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Advisory Board
<ul>
<li>Tips regarding the board candidates</li>
<li>Advisory agreement templates</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Business Development and Sales
<ul>
<li>Sales benchmarks</li>
<li>CRM setup tips &amp; benchmarks</li>
<li>Salesforce compensation structure</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Marketing
<ul>
<li>Marketing audit &amp; checklists</li>
<li>Marketing benchmarks</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Technology
<ul>
<li>High-level code review</li>
<li>Software development reading list and tips</li>
<li>Templates and pre-existing boilerplate solutions</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://applicature.com/shop/consulting/startup-acceleration-advisory/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Your IEO Roadmap</title>
		<link>https://applicature.com/shop/auditing/your-ieo-roadmap</link>
					<comments>https://applicature.com/shop/auditing/your-ieo-roadmap#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nazar.khrupalo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 16:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://applicature.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=3903</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Discover a detailed way to get your project through IEO with our recommendations. Starting with project wrap-up till successful IEO!</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2><b>Why Your Blockchain Initiative Shouldn’t Miss Out on the Action in 2020?</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Initial Exchange Offering (IEO) has opened up new ways to raise funds in the blockchain community. Its main advantage is that the company founders don&#8217;t have to be token sale experts. </span></p>
<p><b>Benefits you get: </b></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">No need to deploy token sale cabinets.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">It is not mandatory to write complicated crowd-sale smart contracts for IEO.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Project promotion to exchange community.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exchange takes care of the entire campaign-launching process.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exchange verifies the AML/KYC compliance.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exchange takes care of the entire campaign-launching process.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><b>However there is a certain list of criteria you would need to follow:</b></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Written and audited Token Smart Contract is “must have” for IEO;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You will have to pass risk audit conducted by exchange: </span>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">set of partnerships and appropriate level of credibility of the project team would be validated manually;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You need to tell a super strong story of your project success;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You cannot start IEO processes without legal opinion.</span></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before being recommended to exchanges for IEO you would be willing to know the answers to the following questions: </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Can I even do an IEO?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">If I can do it, am I ready for an IEO?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Which exchange do I use?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">What can stop me here?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">What would be the expenses?</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It is hard to get exchanges, as they get hundreds of listing requests daily. Hence, you would need to be patient while preparing and finding a perfect match in terms of an exchange to use.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">What we can tell is that the first acquisitions on this super early, emerging market of blockchain technology are happening:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Binance, Bittrex, IDAX, LBank, CoinBene, Coineal, Digifinex, HitBtc have already launched their launchpads for IEO;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">20+ IEOs are published on ICObench today;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over 50 IEOs have already happened!</span></li>
</ul>
<p><b><i>“IEO is a very time sensitive and emerging crypto market niche to penetrate. You’ll want to make it happen in one shot, thus make sure you are ready for it 100%”</i></b></p>
<h2><b>We spotted IEO early on</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We have always been here looking into all possible options and ways to simplify project early-stage lifecycle!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">What has been noted in the scope of our market research and development since November 2018:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><b>The IEO topic raised in Korea in Autumn 2018, </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">and started getting popular among Korean Exchanges;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Binance restarted IEO in February 2019 with the success of BitTorrent, from where this type of fundraising started to get popular;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the last two months market got a slight understanding of what IEO is and what is needed to be successful there. There are still multiple questions based on lack of understanding of the process;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Based on the example of RAID project that lost its partnership with OP.GG several days before planned IEO on Bittrex, and eventually lost their right to run this IEO due to project credibility, we can say: </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;Today, Major Exchanges can provide a proper and in-depth analysis of a project. Potential Token buyers can get more explicit information about the reliability of a Startup, and reactions to malicious activities of the project team are easier to spot&#8221;.</span></i></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The scope of the &#8220;must-have&#8221; project parts had significantly expanded since the days of hyped ICO market. The major metrics of project credibility today are:</span>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">B2B relations</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">reliable partnerships</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">technology determination;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">detailed projects roadmap proving the potential to grow;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">strong story to tell;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">detailed and forward-looking projections of financial profitability;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">And, of course, traction on social media channels among early adopters &amp; investment community;</span></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2><b>We analyzed Market trends and Tokenization Options for you</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We have analyzed more than 2,000 concepts and researched more than 200 scenarios over the past 12 months.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It’s our</span><b> full-time job</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to track innovators who are building blockchain products and key decision-makers in the enterprise world who are hunting for best use cases and avenues for blockchain adoption, as well as the technology to acquire further down the path.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since January 2019, we have picked up our connections with Major Exchanges and gathered all required set of infographics to bring our projects to the table of IEO discussion.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To be honest with you, we discuss crowdfunding campaigns with our clients every day. We have been with projects since 2017, and have guided project teams in the bearish market of autumn 2018 and beginning of 2019. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Everything is telling us that after all we&#8217;ve seen &#8211; 2019 is the time to look for new ways of crowdfunding:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You will have competition that doesn’t sleep. Even though it’s early on, we have seen equally good teams starting similar products, and some of them have raised seed funding and Series A. The space will inevitably become more crowded.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">2019 is the year of first significant acquisitions. It’s already starting slowly, but as the first movers are making their bets, competitors will follow shopping for similar solutions only because that’s how markets work: large players follow each other in their strategic moves.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We are getting closer and closer to the point of mass adoption. It is yet too early to say that it is happening today, however we assume that by year 2030 distributed technologies and crypto currencies will be as common as 3G internet on your mobile phone in 2019.</span></li>
</ul>
<h2><b>What exactly is IEO Review and Recommendations?</b></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We will get into the initial high-level review and validation for IEO</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">After the validation, we will introduce you to the </span><b>Legal Advisor </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">to find out the right path to IEO, and if this path is even available</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A dedicated team of Business Analysts will review your materials for IEO in detail</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We will set up an auditing campaign to get a deep understanding of your current situation, features, maturity, advantages, and potential vulnerabilities</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">To make your project more investment-ready, we will provide you with a set of recommendations for upgrades</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We will emphasize points of attraction and will raise red flags for bottlenecks and pit-holes of the projects </span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Deliverables:</span></p>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Internal Project Review Document.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">360 Recommendations List.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We may forward your project for exchange review in case if it is ready for IEO according to our assessment.</span></li>
</ol>
<p><b>Bonus:</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Set of use cases applicable for your startup enhancement </span></p>
<h2><b>What Will Happen the Next Business Day After You Order?</b></h2>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We will schedule a call with you to dive deep into your situation. The duration of the call could be as long as 2 hours if we need to focus on certain areas of potential explosion. If you cannot dedicate 2 hours in a one-time slot, we will schedule a follow-up call.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">After we have the call, we will set a timeline for preparation of an individualized blueprint for you (usually takes between 5 days and 3 weeks).</span></li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://applicature.com/shop/auditing/your-ieo-roadmap/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Your Blockchain Blueprint</title>
		<link>https://applicature.com/shop/consulting/your-blockchain-blueprint</link>
					<comments>https://applicature.com/shop/consulting/your-blockchain-blueprint#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nazar.khrupalo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 15:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://applicature.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=3658</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Get your individual blockchain use cases solidified in a session with our experts, followed up with an explicit model for your future reference.</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Why Your Blockchain Initiative Won’t Miss Out on the Action in 2020</h2>
<p>2019 has started exactly as we predicted…</p>
<p>First acquisitions on the super early, emerging market of blockchain technology are happening:</p>
<ul>
<li>Facebook has announced the acquisition of ChainSpace</li>
<li>Bakkt, backed by the New York Stock Exchange, has proceeded with its first acquisition in Starbucks</li>
</ul>
<h2>We Knew Blockchain Was Here to Stay</h2>
<p>Blockchain is now disrupting and penetrating all business verticals!</p>
<p>Huge payers like<strong> C.H. Robinson, UPS Supply Chain Solutions, Walmart, British Airways, FedEx, Maersk, Ford, Nestle, BHP Billiton, JPMorganChase, HSBC, Bank of America, MoneyGram, American Express, Coral Health, SimplyVitalHealth, Robomed, Patientory, Center for Disease Control and Prevention, Nebula Genomics, EncrypGen, Iryo, BlockPharma, Guardtime, Burtiq, Factom, Disney, Time Warner</strong>, whose business models are being followed and adopted globally, have already got their blockchain use cases <strong>LIVE!<br />
</strong><br />
<strong>Toyota, Samsung, BNP Paribas, VISA, Western Union, 21st Century Fox, CBS, Comcast, Viacom and Live Nation Entertainment, Columbia Records, and Sony BMG</strong> are currently working on use cases for<em> adopting blockchain and will start utilizing it for their businesses in 2019!<br />
</em><br />
Are you already there?</p>
<h2>We Have Worked Hard to Become Your Expert Guides</h2>
<p>We have analyzed more than 2,000 concepts and researched more than 200 scenarios in the last 12 months.</p>
<p>Due to our relations with EEA and the Linux Foundation, we have access to early industry news.</p>
<p>It’s our<strong> full-time job</strong> to track innovators who are building blockchain products and key decision-makers in the enterprise world who are hunting for best use cases and avenues for blockchain adoption as well as the technology to acquire further down the path.</p>
<p>Reading the news, you are probably asking yourself whether YOUR BLOCKCHAIN CONCEPT WILL BE ACQUIRED? OR CAN IT BE SUCCESSFUL AT ALL?</p>
<p>Let’s be frank. We receive a lot of b.s inquiries. All the token-sale hype has driven crowds of people into the industry and given them a good excuse to call themselves blockchain-based companies. We have also seen really good teams, projects, and companies evolve over the months and years.</p>
<p>Everything is telling us 2019 is the best time to validate and start your blockchain venture, because:</p>
<ul>
<li>You will have competition that doesn’t sleep. Even though it’s early on, we have seen equally good teams starting similar products, and some of them have raised seed funding and Series A.The space will inevitably become more crowded.</li>
<li>2019 is the year of first significant acquisitions. It’s already starting slowly, but as the first movers are making their bets. Competitors will follow shopping for similar solutions just because that’s how markets work: large players follow each other in their strategic moves.</li>
<li>There’s blood in the street. We are at the bottom of the cryptocurrency markets cycles. It’s just a good time to create a company or product that is in this market in terms of uptrends.</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Build without Losing</h3>
<p><em>Every use case you get could be potentially a new branch of your project development to attract interest. Order now to get possible use cases for your Platform.</em></p>
<h2>What exactly is Included in Your Blueprint?</h2>
<ul>
<li>List of most prominent blockchain use cases applicable to your business</li>
<li>High-level analysis of business advantages from blockchain implementation</li>
<li>Market use cases of similar solutions and how you can stand out from the crowd</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Bonus:</strong><br />
Honest Insider Review of the Most Popular Blockchain Solutions</p>
<h2>What Will Happen the Next Business Day After You Order?</h2>
<ol>
<li>We will schedule a call with you to dive deep into your situation. The duration of the call could be as long as 2 hours if we need to focus on certain areas of potential explosion. If you cannot dedicate 2 hours in one-time slot, we will schedule a follow-up call.</li>
<li>After we have the call, we will set a timeline for preparation of an individualized blueprint for you (usually takes between 2 days and 1.5 weeks).</li>
</ol>
<h3>Why It’s Risk Free</h3>
<p>We have a 100% return policy on this product. If, for any reason, our work doesn’t turn to be a good fit for you, we will refund your payment for this product, no questions asked. We do this because we are confident we can help you progress. We value successful partnerships more than anything else.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://applicature.com/shop/consulting/your-blockchain-blueprint/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
